How is it?
Good!
Is anyone home?
Yes!
Coming...
Dai-chan, long time no see.
Haruko!
What are you doing here?
Rin-chan!
Reina-chan?!
What's going on, Reina-chan?
Are you going somewhere?
Haruko...
Uh-uh. We came to visit.
Oh, really?
Um...
Reina-chan, do you like sweet buns?
What's that?
Round sweets.
Then I like it!
Then Rin, pour some barley
tea for Reina-chan.
Okay. Reina-chan, let's go.
You came right during snack time!
I wanna eat snacks, too!
I dunno about tomorrow.
It's different than a sacrifice. Something's off.
I don't think it's like some penalty game.
So, why? I don't get it at all.
I'm a little bit unsatisfied, but your presence
right now is more than just important.
There's no such thing in this world
as something never-ending.
Crying isn't painful, it's love's sweet drops, sweet drops!
I want to keep dreaming forever, ya know?
I want to be more kind, ya know?
As long as I’m with you, I’m happy.
Girls sure are strong, ya know?
But sometimes we're weak, ya know?
Our wish is to be happy, happy, happy!
And those days will be happy, too!
Just wanna make you happy!
Yummy!
I know, right?
This is the first time I've had it!
Thank you.
Wow. This is my first time here,
but it's like Grandpa's house...
More importantly, what's wrong?
You bring a school satchel
over on a Sunday...
Sorry.
Actually, we... ran away from home.
Wh-wh-wha...?!
The folks at the house will worry!
Why would you do that?!
Is it... uh... you know...?
Is it what?!
Y-You know. Your husband...
That's part of it.
Part of it?
Part of it!
And is there something
with his parents there...
That's part of it, too!
I-I guess it's difficult living
with your husband's parents...?
I wonder if peaceful cohabitation
between a wife and her in-laws even exists...
Scary!
I have no brothers or sisters and
there's nowhere else for me to go.
That's the arithmetic book we use, too!
Can we stay here, Dai-chan?
Really?
Let me see your other textbooks, too!
F-First, let's talk things through.
Sure. Um...
Now what about your in-laws?
Your Japanese book is
different than mine!
It's okay.
I left a note.
I wanna see yours!
I didn't say where we
were going, though...
Sure, let's go!
And I'll take Reina to school...
Other than that...
I haven't given it much thought.
I haven't even told my parents yet...
Haven't given it much thought?
You've got your daughter with you...
Haruko...
Well, I had no other choice!
I just had to get out of that house!
I couldn't stand it another second!
Fine...
For now, why don't we go
grocery shopping for tonight?
Dai-chan...
I don't have anything, but you
can use the room on the right.
It really is different!
Thank you. It's a little heavy.
What the hell did you cram in here?!
Reina's slippers and textbooks
are in there, too...
I'm surprised you made it this far.
Dai-chan, usually you just make
do with whatever, right?
Well, tonight I'll cook
you a decent meal.
I do not "just make do"!
Daikichi, can we look at the sweets?
You can each choose one thing.
Okay!
What kind of meat should we get?
It's all the same to me.
Not that one!
This one.
No, this one's a little...
Daikichi-san! Hello.
Dai-chan, this ground beef and
pork combo is really cheap...
Oh, crap!
Uh... This isn't what it looks like!
This is Haruko, my cousin
from my mother's side!
Who cares what "side" I'm from?
O-Oh, really?
Nice to meet you!
My son is a classmate of Rin-chan, and
I'm always obliged to Daikichi-san...
What the hell am I saying?!
She didn't ask who it was!
Why did I feel the need
to explain it to her?!
Oh? Then my daughter is the same age.
Oh, really?
"This isn't what it looks
like!" What the hell...?!
I'm Reina!
She's a first-grader
from this year, so...
I'm Kouki.
Oh, my!
Yo, Kouki!
What kind of sweets did you pick?
What's up, Daikichi!
This one!
Deluxe Big Nyan Gum!
I'm getting vegetable sponge cake!
I'm getting Meow Meow Kitty candy!
Are those really sweets?!
She's pretty, isn't she?
Y-Yeah, I suppose she's one
of the more attractive moms...
But I don't think you should
have an affair with her!
A-Are you out of your mind?!
It's not like that at all!
In the first place, she has enough trouble
just taking care of Kouki on her own,
so who has time...
"On her own"?!
So during lunch at school...
Dope!
You watch too many weird dramas!
Uh-huh?
A bug got out of its cage!
I'm guessing she's two or three
years older than we are...
W-What the hell do I care
about how old she is?!
Really?!
So, is she divorced?
I don't know the details...
It looks delicious!
I haven't had this before!
I experimented some.
Usually, everything is made
to my mother-in-law's taste.
Mama, I wanna have this at home, too!
Well, thank you for the
food we're about to eat.
Thank you for the food
we're about to eat!
we're about to eat...
It's good!
Thank you, Rin-chan!
Come on, Reina. Hold your
chopsticks properly.
Okay!
The floor creaks!
Here, Reina, use this towel!
Okay!
What's that?
A bra!
Hey, Reina!
Don't pull on it like that!
Did they fall asleep?
Yeah, finally...
It seems they were both excited.
I moved Rin-chan to
your futon, Dai-chan.
Thank you...
Thanks.
That's delicious!
It's been so long since I had alcohol.
Want something to eat?
I gain weight easily
these days, so no thanks.
I'm not surprised...
Then I have gained weight?!
No, no, not that.
I just meant, now that
we've hit our thirties...
I'd be happy just to be 30 again...
You can't act the same as when
you were younger, you know?
You've gotta be careful.
On the other hand, my husband
doesn't look at me anymore...
It's like, who am I
making an effort for?
Haruko...
What?
While you were all taking a
bath, I called your house.
Why?!
Don't do anything weird, Dai-chan!
It's not weird.
You want everyone there
to worry about you?!
All I said was that you two were fine
and are going to stay here for a while.
I didn't even give my address.
I told you already, I left a note!
So leave me alone!
It's not about you.
You can do what you want, but
there's Reina to consider.
Reina's with me and she's doing
fine, so there's no problem!
Even if that's true, if you don't tell
them where you are and that Reina's okay,
how the hell are the people
who are waiting gonna know?
I don't care about the
people who are waiting...
You need to be a little more
level-headed about this.
Do you just wanna make
trouble for your family?!
Rin-chan!
Come in here!
Okay!
That's my nose!
Papa and Mama are always fighting.
Even though they're married?
Yeah. Even though they're married, but
I always pretend like I'm sleeping...
Let's jumble up!
Okay.
That tickles!
That's my cheek!
Every day, I...
Ever since I got married, I've been
living with my feelings bottled up!
I think I deserve to cause them
at least a little trouble!
Sorry, Dai-chan.
I shouldn't have said those things.
It's okay...
I'm going to bed.
Dai-chan...
Dai-chan, good night.
Good night.
Rin-chan...
Good morning!
Good morning...
Rin-chan, are you making breakfast?
Uh-huh.
Daikichi, good morning!
You're up early today, huh?
Yeah, well...
Hey, Dai-chan!
You have Rin-chan make breakfast?!
W-What do you think I am?!
We always cook together!
And when we use the stove, I...
Be nice to each other!
Look, you've got rice on your face.
Don't take too long eating.
We're going to school by train today...
Rin-chan!
What is it? This early in the morning...
It's Kouki-kun!
Yeah, yeah!
Just come in!
You're disturbing the neighbors!
Is your school far, Rin-chan?
You already have to leave?
Uh-uh.
Kouki's mom is busy, so he
always comes over early.
G-Good morning.
Daikichi, did you get married?!
Of course not! She's my cousin!
Oh. Then like I figured, you're
not gonna get married, huh?
What's "like I figured"
supposed to mean?!
Daikichi, do you wanna get married?
Look, I don't even know...
Mama, for you, single is better, right?
What's "single"?
It's not getting married.
I know that one! "Divorce", right?!
I don't know "divorce"!
Reina-chan, your mom is married
but single is better...
Daikichi, you're single, but
is married better for you?
Adults really are weird, you know?
They are, aren't they?
Daikichi, can I have a rice ball?
You had breakfast before
coming, didn't you?
Yeah.
Fine, have one.
It was supposed to be for me, though...
Yes!!
You didn't eat breakfast?
Why did you eat again?
You're good-natured
to a fault, Dai-chan.
What's the problem?
I had one because I wanted one!
What, 'cause I gave him a rice ball?
You're strange.
No, not that.
Hah?
You must be just as
busy as she is, right?
You really must have a thing
for that beautiful mother...
St-Stu... Dumbass!
That again?!
I just thought I could help
her out a little, is all...
And Rin gets along with them, too, so...
But that's all it is.
I don't know the details,
but I'm pretty sure Kouki and his
mother have been through a lot.
It would be rude of
me to be too forward.
It must be hard, being
a woman on her own...
Reina! I told you before, if you
don't hurry up, you're gonna be late!
Mama always has just one piece of toast.
Haruko...
She says she's on a diet.
Good morning!
Good morning.
It's a secret that we're
staying with Daikichi.
Why?
Because I said so! Understand?
Okay!
Good morning!
Reina-chan, did you
come with your mother?
Yeah, that's right!
We secretly ran away from home,
so I came by train today!
What the...?!
Wait!
Hey!
Didn't I tell you to
hold onto it tight?!
I'm not gonna get another one for you!
But maybe it'll get home before us!
Maybe! Maybe it will...
Have a nice evening.
Huh? You're working late.
Yeah, my husband's watching him at home.
Oh. How's Yuu-kun doing?
He's fine!
Actually, he's so rambunctious these
days, he's more than I can handle.
But it's nice that your
husband helps out.
This is the first time!
His business trip was suddenly
rescheduled, so he has the day off.
Oh...
There's no way I can rely on
my husband to raise our kid.
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Reina-chan is waiting!
Okay, okay...
We're home! Reina-chan!
They fell asleep right away tonight.
Haruko, don't tell me...
You don't intend to make a
big thing of this, do you?
Oh, you mean divorce
or something like that?
Yeah, that.
No, no. That won't happen.
W-What the hell? I wasted
time worrying about it.
Well, I have thought about
it any number of times...
In fact, I think about
it almost every day...
After all, if I come to think
of my husband as the enemy
while living in his family's house...
Except for Reina, they're
all enemies to me.
I think of just the two of us as family.
But that isn't being realistic, is it?
There's Reina... and the question
of my ability to earn a living...
And all the problems I'd have to face
before I could reach that point...
In my case, at the end of the day, it
looks like I'm better off where I am.
I got engaged soon after
I joined the company...
When I was young, all I thought
about was becoming a good wife.
I have no choice... do I?
And that's the only way
I can protect Reina...
You know, I've never been married,
but it seems like it's hard,
even for a normal family.
Dai-chan, you do it all by yourself.
It's amazing.
Nah, I haven't been able
to do anything for her.
That's not true. Rin-chan
looks really happy.
When she's cooking for
you, for example...
Kouki-kun and his mom are doing their
best too, with just the two of them.
So Reina and I can hang in there.
All this "the two of us"...
Do you talk to your husband about this?
Mmm, he works overtime every night and
we never have a decent conversation.
That's why Reina and I will do our best.
Besides, I've been putting
up with it for years now.
I'm sure I can keep at it.
As long as I try to not feel anything,
I can hold out, more or less.
That sounds really unhealthy...
It's just the opposite!
My health would be messed
up if I didn't do that.
You've gotten stronger, Haruko...
Mmm, I don't know about that...
After you give birth and raise a kid,
there are times when you need
enormous strength, right?
Especially when they're still a baby...
I don't know what it's
like with a baby, but...
And while you're keeping
that up, for some reason...
You naturally become like this.
I really don't wanna be an old woman...
I never wanted to become
strong, especially...
If I could, I'd be a girl forever...
I'm sorry, Dai-chan.
Thank you.
We'll go home tomorrow.
I see...
What is "marriage"?
What does it mean to become a parent?
What's wrong?
It's your turn, Reina.
I knew it!
What?
Papa's car!
Papa's coming after
he finishes his work.
You know he wouldn't be this early.
I'm positive it's Papa!
I'm not wrong!
It's not him, I say! Reina!
Papa!
I was worried about you, Reina.
I was worried, too!
Sorry.
What? So if he wants to get off
work at this time, he can, huh?
Hey, don't put it like that!
It's tough working for a company, too...
Stupid Hideyuki-san...
I apologize.
Haruko caused you so much trouble...
Oh, no, no... I didn't really...
I really don't know what to say...
I'm wearing the wrong clothes!
Thanks a lot, Dai-chan.
You'd think Papa would at
least carry our bags, right?
He's so inconsiderate.
I know! He's inconsirit!
If you ever feel like it,
you can come back anytime.
Oh... I can't put you out
more than I already have.
No... That's not what I mean.
Rin is always saying that
she wants to see Reina-chan.
Thank you... Dai-chan...
Mama! Mama!
Then can we come again on Sunday?
L-Listen, Reina...
When she was a girl,
Haruka was a crybaby.
Last night, she muttered that she
wanted to stay a girl forever.
Well...
Next time you come, why
not pack a little lighter?
I hate even looking at that bag.
Impossible!
Girls always have a heavy load to bear.
This is nothing.
Bye-bye!
I'll see you off!
A sunny early Sunday afternoon
Let's go somewhere today
It's the same road I'm used to traveling
But I can see it sparkling so bright
With the sun shining down its warmth
And you here by my side...
I'm already high, high, high
I feel like dashing out
Sing, la, la, la
My voice out to forever
I'm already high, high, high
Ride the dancing wind
Sing, la, la, la
My voice springs up
How about this one?
Yeah!
But maybe this one suits
you more, Rin-chan...
Here, what do you think?
Can I try this one on too?
Yes, sure.
I'm thirsty!
She just has to try this one on...
Oh, don't you like this one?!
Um, Kouki and I are gonna stroll around.
Okay!
See, this one is really you!
Let's go.
You look so cute, Rin-chan!
That good?
It tastes like summer!
I hear ya!